Sigma Pi Phi, Beta Psi Boul; Records apap333
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Special Events, 1985-2011; 3; 1.9 cubic ft.
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Name Tags, Ribbons and Registration signs, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 6)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Newsclipping, 2003 (Oversized 4)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Paid Registration, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 7)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference Plan, 2002-2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 8)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Reports and Policy Resolution, 2003-2004 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 9)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Report of Officers, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 10)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Summary Report, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 11)
  - 15th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Update Presentation Drafts, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 12)
  - 16th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference: Report of Officers, 2005 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 13)
  - 17th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 14)
  - 19th Biennial Northeast Regional Conference, 2011 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 15 - 16)
  - Albany Ambassador Award, 2003-2004 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 17)
  - Albany County Convention and Visitors Bureau: Conference Planning Guide, 2003-2004 (Cd 3)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees, 2001-2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 18-20)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Albany County Convention and Visitors Bureau Binder, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 21)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Contracts, 2002-2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 22)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Correspondences, 2001-2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 23)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Exhibits Committee, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 24)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Hotel Package offers, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 25-26)
  - Beta Psi Regional Planning Committees: Preliminary Reports to Regional Committee, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Special Events), Folder 27)
  - Biennial Grand Boulé, 1984-2010 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 1-2)
  - Biennial Grand Boulé: Official Photo, 1984 (Flat-file 2)
  - Biennial Grand Boulé, 1992 (Video-tape 1)
  - National/Regional Reports, 1982-1983; 1985; 2002-2003; 2005 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 3)
  - Northeast Region Executive Committee, 1985-2009 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 4-5)
  - Northeast Regional Conference Memorabilia, 2003; 2011 (Oversized 4)
  - Northeast Regional Conferences, 1985; 1987; 1989-1990; 2003 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 6)
  - Sigma Pi Phi Grand Officers and Executive Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 7)
  - Sigma Pi Phi Membership Directory, 1995 (Box 2 (3-Special Events), Folder 8)
- Publications, 1983-2014; 4; 3.0 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically
  The Publications series consists of The Boulé Journal which is a quarterly publication compiled by Sigma Pi Phi’s Grand Boulé. It is the fraternity’s official publication and subordinate Boulés' submit items for consideration. The publications span from 1983 to 2013 and are almost a complete collection of issues published in those years. The series does not contain any issues published in 1989.
  - The Boulé Journal, 1983 Winter-1984 Spring (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1984 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 2)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1985 Summer (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 3)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1986 Spring (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 4)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1986 Summer (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 5)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1986 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1986 Winter (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1987 Spring (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 8)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1987 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 9)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1987 Winter (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 10)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1988 Spring (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 11)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1988 Summer (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 12)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1988 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 13)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1988 Winter (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 14)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1990 Spring (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 15)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1990 Summer (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 16)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1990 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 17)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1991 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 18)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1992 Summer (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 19)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1992 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 20)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1992 Winter (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 21)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1993 Spring (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 22)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1993 Summer (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 23)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1993 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 24)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1994 Summer (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 25)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1994 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 26)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1995 Spring (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 27)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1995 Summer (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 28)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1995 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 29)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1995 Winter (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 30)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1996 Spring (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 31)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1996 Summer (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 32)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1996 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 33)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1996 Winter (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 34)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1997 Spring (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 35)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1997 Summer (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 36)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1997 Fall (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 37)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1997 Winter (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 38)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1998 Spring (Box 1 (4-Publications), Folder 39)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1998 Summer (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1998 Fall (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 2)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1999 Spring (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 3)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1999 Fall (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 4)
  - The Boulé Journal, 1999 Winter (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 5)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2000 Spring (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2000 Summer (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2000 Fall (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 8)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2000 Winter (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 9)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2001 Spring (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 10)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2001 Summer (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 11)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2001 Fall (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 12)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2001 Winter (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 13)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2002 Spring (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 14)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2002 Summer (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 15)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2002 Fall (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 16)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2002 Winter (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 17)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2003 Spring (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 18)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2003 Summer (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 19)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2003 Fall (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 20)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2003 Winter (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 21)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2004 Summer (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 22)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2004 Fall (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 23)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2004 Winter (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 24)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2005 Spring (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 25)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2005 Summer (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 26)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2005 Fall (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 27)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2005 Winter (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 28)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2006 Summer (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 29)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2006 Fall (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 30)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2006 Winter (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 31)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2007 Spring (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 32)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2007 Summer (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 33)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2007 Fall (Box 2 (4-Publications), Folder 34)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2007 Winter (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2008 Spring (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 2)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2008 Summer (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 3)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2008 Fall (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 4)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2008 Winter (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 5)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2009 Spring (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2009 Summer (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2009 Fall (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 8)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2009 Winter (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 9)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2010 Spring (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 10)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2010 Summer (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 11)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2010 Fall (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 12)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2010 Winter (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 13)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2011 Spring (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 14)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2011 Summer (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 15)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2011 Fall (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 16)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2011 Winter (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 17)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2012 Spring (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 18)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2012 Summer (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 19)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2012 Fall (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 20)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2012 Winter (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 21)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2013 Spring (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 22)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2013 Summer (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 23)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2013 Fall (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 24)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2013 Winter (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 25)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2014 Spring (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 26)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2014 Summer (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 27)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2014 Fall (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 28)
  - The Boulé Journal, 2014 Winter (Box 3 (4-Publications), Folder 29)